A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- "Lungs at Work" No Smoking Sign 1988, 1-sign (Box-folder 400:001)
- A Health Message: Series by the NTA N.D., 15-D (Box-folder 400:002)
- Christmas Seals Stickers 2009, 4-sheets (Box-folder 400:003)
- Christmas Seals Greeting Cards 2009, 5-D (Box-folder 400:004)
- Christmas Seals Poster 2009, 4-D (Box-folder 400:005)
- Christmas Seals Calendar 2010, 2-D (Box-folder 400:006)
- "Lungs at Work" Campaign Folder N.D., 7-D (Box-folder 400:007)
- Christmas Seals Calendar 1988, 2-D (Box-folder 400:008)
- "Este es el Sr. Germen De TB" N.D., 2-D (Box-folder 400:009)
- "This is Mr. TB Germ" N.D., 10-D (Box-folder 400:010)
- ALA Information Folder N.D., 1-D (Box-folder 400:011)
- Christmas Seals Placemat 1959, 1-D (Box-folder 400:012)
- "TB Facts" leaflets N.D., 2-D (Box-folder 400:013)
- ALAV Information Brochures N.D., 7-D (Box-folder 400:014)
- "Lung Hazards on the Job" series N.D., 10-D (Box-folder 400:015)
- "Facts about your Lungs" series N.D., 28-D (Box-folder 400:016)
- "50 Years of Christmas Seals" N.D., 1-D (Box-folder 400:017)
- Christmas Seals Publicity Kit 1986, 1-D (Box-folder 400:018)
- Christmas Seals Bookmark N.D., 1-D (Box-folder 400:019)
- Christmas Seals Poster 1989, 1-D (Box-folder 400:020)
- Christmas Seals Poster 1984, 1-D (Box-folder 400:021)
- Christmas Seals Poster 1992, 1-D (Box-folder 400:022)
- Christmas Seals (multiple sheets) 1907, 1914, 1916, 1919, 1920-1952, multiple sheets (Box-folder 401)
- Christmas Seals (multiple sheets) 1953-1970, multiple sheets (Box-folder 402)
- Christmas Seals (multiple sheets) 1971-1980, multiple sheets (Box-folder 403)
- Christmas Seals (multiple sheets) 1980-1987, multiple sheets (Box-folder 404)
- Christmas Seals (multiple sheets) 1987-2009, multiple sheets (Box-folder 405)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1972, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:001)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1976, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:002)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1977, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:003)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1978, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:004)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1979, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:005)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1980, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:006)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1981, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:007)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1982, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:008)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1983, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:009)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1984, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:010)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1986, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:011)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1987, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:012)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1988, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:013)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1989, 1-scarf (Box-folder 406:014)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1990, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:001)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1991, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:002)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1993, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:003)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1994, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:004)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1995, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:005)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1996, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:006)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1997, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:007)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1998, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:008)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 1999, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:009)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 2000, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:010)
- Christmas Seal Scarf 2001, 1-scarf (Box-folder 407:011)
- ALAV Stamps and Press (multiple sizes) N.D., 65-items (Box-folder 408)
- Christmas Seals Ornament 2009, 2-ornaments (Box-folder 409:001)
- Christopher Radko Ornament N.D., 1-ornament (Box-folder 409:002)
- Christmas Seals Coffee Mug 2000, 1-mug (Box-folder 409:003)
- Christmas Seals Lapel Pin 2009, 2-pins (Box-folder 409:004)
- Christmas Seals Lapel Pin 1989, 2-pins (Box-folder 409:005)
- Modern Health Crusader Pins N.D., 10-pins (Box-folder 409:006)
- ALA Health Messages Buttons N.D., 16-buttons (Box-folder 409:007)
- ALA Health Folding Lapel Pins N.D., 9-pins (Box-folder 409:008)
- ALA Health Clasp Pins N.D., 25-pins (Box-folder 409:009)
- ALA Health Signs N.D., 5-signs (Box-folder 409:010)
- "Rule out TB" Ruler N.D., 1-ruler (Box-folder 409:011)
- Christmas Seals Commemorative Plates and one engraving block N.D., 5-plates, 1 engraving block (Box-folder 410)
  The wood and metal engraving block is for Christmas seals made in 1963. It was donated in January 1992 by Judith Robinson. It has an artifact number: artifacts01797.
- Christmas Seals Decorative Tiles 1907, 1972-1973, 1975-1983, 1985-1987, 23-tiles (Box-folder 411)
- ALAV Framed Certificates and Photographs N.D., 7-frames (Box-folder 412 [oversize])
- ALAV Framed Portraits N.D., 7-frames (Box-folder 413 [oversize])
- ALAV Framed Portraits N.D., 8-frames (Box-folder 414 [oversize])
- ALAV Framed Portraits and Needlepoint N.D., 10-frames (Box-folder 415 [oversize])
- ALAV Framed Posters and Certificates N.D., 3-frames (Box-folder 416 [oversize])
- TB Information 1930s-1970s, TDoc (Box-folder 417:001 [oversize])
- ALA Education Booklets 2000-2004, TDoc (Box-folder 417:002 [oversize])
- TB Testing Forms N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:003 [oversize])
- Reported TB Data 1971, TDoc (Box-folder 417:004 [oversize])
- Reported TB Data 1969, TDoc (Box-folder 417:005 [oversize])
- Reported TB Data 1970, TDoc (Box-folder 417:006 [oversize])
- Handbook for TB Workers N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:007 [oversize])
- Data on TB in Virginia 1973, TDoc (Box-folder 417:008 [oversize])
- History of the National Conference of TB Workers N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:009 [oversize])
- Health Education Opportunities for TB Assoc. N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:010 [oversize])
- Board Members Against TB N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:011 [oversize])
- TB: Diagnosis, Treatment and Control N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:012 [oversize])
- "Women are Kicking the Cigarette Habit: Find Out How and Why" 1978, TDoc (Box-folder 417:013 [oversize])
- Appraisal Now: Guidelines for Evaulating the Effectiveness of Your Official Air Pollution Control Program N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:014 [oversize])
- Photochemical Oxidants: An Air Pollution Health Effects Report N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:015 [oversize])
- A New Perspective on the Lung: A Seminar for Science and Medical Writers 1973, TDoc (Box-folder 417:016 [oversize])
- A Study of TB Clinics in Five Areas 1971, TDoc (Box-folder 417:017 [oversize])
- An Introduction to Respiratory Diseases 1964, TDoc (Box-folder 417:018 [oversize])
- Lung Disease Changes Everything N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:019 [oversize])
- Lung Disease Data 1998-1999, TDoc (Box-folder 417:020 [oversize])
- Childhood Asthma: A Matter of Control N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:021 [oversize])
- Freedom from Smoking in Twenty Days N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:022 [oversize])
- TB: What the Physician Should Know 1986, TDoc (Box-folder 417:023 [oversize])
- Help Yourself to Better Breathing N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:024 [oversize])
- Populations at Risk N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:025 [oversize])
- What Every Physical Educator Should Know about Asthma N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:026 [oversize])
- Health Hazards in Arts and Crafts 1982, TDoc (Box-folder 417:027 [oversize])
- In the News: A Manual for Newspaper Writing 1947, TDoc (Box-folder 417:028 [oversize])
- The Health Costs for Air Pollution 1967-1977, TDoc (Box-folder 417:029 [oversize])
- Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disesase N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:030 [oversize])
- Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disesase N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:030 [oversize])
- Breathing: What You Need to Know 1968, TDoc (Box-folder 417:031 [oversize])
- Air Pollution Primer N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:032 [oversize])
- Nursing and Respiratory Diseases 1968, TDoc (Box-folder 417:033 [oversize])
- Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease Manual for Physicians 1963, TDoc (Box-folder 417:034 [oversize])
- Chronic Obstructive Emphysema Disease Manual for Physicians 1963, TDoc (Box-folder 417:035 [oversize])
- TB Tine Test in Infection and Disease 1965, TDoc (Box-folder 417:036 [oversize])
- The Long Adventure: Chapters in the Story of TB Control 1946, TDoc (Box-folder 417:037 [oversize])
- The Changing Years: the Story of the Crusade to Control TB N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:038 [oversize])
- TB Control Programs 1955, TDoc (Box-folder 417:039 [oversize])
- TB Association: It's Organization and Administration 1954, TDoc (Box-folder 417:040 [oversize])
- Building a Community Program for TB Control 1950, TDoc (Box-folder 417:041 [oversize])
- People Against Lung Disease N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:042 [oversize])
- Help Fight TB 1947, TDoc (Box-folder 417:043 [oversize])
- Twenty Years of Medical Research 1943, TDoc (Box-folder 417:044 [oversize])
- TB Resources and Related Papers N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 417:045 [oversize])
- TB Resources and Misc. Papers 1990s, TDoc (Box-folder 417:046 [oversize])
- TB Education Resources and Misc. Papers 1990s, TDoc (Box-folder 417:047 [oversize])
- The Tuberculosis Association, Its Organization and Administration 1949, pamphlet (Box-folder 417:047 [oversize])
- TB Education Resources and Misc. Papers 1960s-1970s, TDoc (Box-folder 418:001 [oversize])
- TB Study 1960, TDoc (Box-folder 418:002 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1954, TDoc (Box-folder 418:003 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1955, TDoc (Box-folder 418:004 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1956, TDoc (Box-folder 418:005 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1957, TDoc (Box-folder 418:006 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1958, TDoc (Box-folder 418:007 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1959, TDoc (Box-folder 418:008 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1961, TDoc (Box-folder 418:009 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1962, TDoc (Box-folder 418:010 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1963, TDoc (Box-folder 418:011 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1964, TDoc (Box-folder 418:012 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1965, TDoc (Box-folder 418:013 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1966, TDoc (Box-folder 418:014 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1967, TDoc (Box-folder 418:015 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1968, TDoc (Box-folder 418:016 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1969, TDoc (Box-folder 418:017 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1970, TDoc (Box-folder 418:018 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1971, TDoc (Box-folder 418:019 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1972, TDoc (Box-folder 418:020 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1974, TDoc (Box-folder 418:021 [oversize])
- TB Reports and Data 1973, TDoc (Box-folder 418:022 [oversize])
- TB Association of Petersburg N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 418:023 [oversize])
- Blue Ridge TB Association N.D., TDoc (Box-folder 418:024 [oversize])
- Rita Quinn 1984-85, 3 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:001)
- School presentation by Elaine Slattenmeyer February 1987, 10 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:002)
- Art Auction, Smoking at the Workplace Presentation, Military Traffic Management Command 1986, 18 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:003)
- 1986 Annual Meeting 1986, 19 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:004)
- Terri Brown and Bob Sally, Cora Kelly Magnet School Students, Winners of Kids for Clean Air Contest N.D., 8 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:005)
- Pearl Bailey and a caroling fest November 20, 1985, 7 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:006)
- Clean Air Week Snifter Presentation, Bob Sally at Mt. Daniel Elementary 1986, 15 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:007)
- Letters to Frosty Award Winners December 20, 1985, 12 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:008)
- Jacqueline Morgan Elementary School Presentation March 1985, 10 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:009)
- Washington Redskins football player Charlie Brown and Son April 17, 1985, 4 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:010)
- Jacqueline Morgan and Lincolnia Community Center Octopuff Presentation July 1985, 12 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:011)
- SSC Grads--Allan Hudson, Samantha Browne--Letter, Richard Parrot & Ray & Rita Quinn Robert Seward 1984, 5 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:012)
- SAID, Inc. April 10, 1985, 9 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:013)
- Terri Miller/Andrewa Cremins, Metromedia Cable, Alice Schomburg (volunteer) N.D., 5 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:014)
- Wilma Schmidt N.D., 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 419:015)
- Dr. Larry Miller, Shriners of Bristol (?) Club, Pat Bischofy (Bischoff?) N.D., 19 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:016)
- Apnea Monitor Baby, Matthew McClain June 1984, 1 B&W photo, negatives (Box-folder 419:017)
- Potomac Lung Association N.D., 25 photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:018)
- Fairfax Nursing Center ALANV Mantua Women's Group 1988, 4 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:019)
- C.O.P.D. Estate P. Seminar November 1984, 10 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:020)
- C.O.P.D. Workshop June 1984, 6 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:021)
- "Asthma Worshop for Kids" June 1984, 6 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:022)
- Occupational Health N.D., 4 B&W photos from publication (Box-folder 419:023)
- Art Hammarstrom & Donald A. Baskerville, C.O.P.D. November 1984, 3 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:024)
- "Asthma Worshop for Kids" June 1984, 6 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:022)
- Occupational Health N.D., 4 B&W photos from publication (Box-folder 419:023)
- Art Hammarstrom & Donald A. Baskerville, C.O.P.D. November 1984, 3 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:024)
- "Stop Smoking Presentation for Kids" 1984, 2 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:025)
- Clean Air Week May 6-13, 1984, 7 B&W photos, negative (Box-folder 419:026)
  Mrs. Bozman; Sample smoking machine, VTRDA; "With his oxygen tank close by, John Lacy takes a look at Clean Air Week promotional meterials. Lacy has one lung and emphysema. He, along with two other representatives with lung disease, are speaking out against the danger of air pollution." "Albert W. Starkweather Brownville, New York, 13615, Burning peony tops, wasting humus and polluting the air."
- Smoking and Pregnancy N.D., 2 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:027)
- ALA of Northern Virginia, sign August 1981, 2 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:028)
- WPWC Radio "Issues in Our Life", Bob Sally and Sandy Sanduon (?) March 8, 1985, 3 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:029)
- WNVT TV "Afternoon Repast" smoking debate bob Sally, John Banzatt, John Flannery February 22, 1985, 8 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:030)
- Rita Quinn, Sid Caesar ALA Annual Meeting May 22, 1984, 4 B&W photos, 1 Tmemo (Box-folder 419:031)
- Annual Meeting Open House 1983, 14 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:032)
- Steven M. Zimmet, M.D. 1984, 18 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:033)
- ALANV Annual Meeting 1983-1984, 9 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:034)
- Sid Caesar Quality International Promo N.D., 1 B&W photo, negative (Box-folder 419:035)
- Freedom from Smoking ad and sign stating "This area reserved for our non-smoking patrons" N.D., 1 B&W photo, 1 sign (Box-folder 419:036)
- Tarah Shawa Grant & Santa Claus, "Letters to Santa" contest December 1984, 18 B&W photos, negatives (Box-folder 419:037)
- Estate Planning Seminar April 26, 1984, 3 B&W photos from publication (Box-folder 419:038)
- Art show and Auction of ALA Northern Virginia, Fairfax VA May 31, 1984, 7 B&W photos (Box-folder 419:039)
- Emily P. Bissel N.D., 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 419:040)
- Christmas Seals 1983, 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 419:041)
- NTRDA Crusade of the Christmas Seal N.D., 4 pamphlets (Box-folder 420:001)
- The Message of the Double-Barred Cross c1949, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:002)
- The Anti-TB Record: A Report to the Public by the Anti-Tuberculosis league of Norfolk 1956, 2 TD (Box-folder 420:003)
- ALA The Pictorial History of Christmas Seals c1976, 2 pamphlets (Box-folder 420:004)
- Script for "The Need Continues" 1984 March 22, 1 TD (Box-folder 420:005)
- ALA Christmas Seal Chairman Milestone Parade 1985, 1 brochure (Box-folder 420:006)
- Airways, quarterly publication of ALAV 1988 Winter, 5 bulletins (Box-folder 420:007)
- Southeastern Virginia Tuberculosis and Health Association Annual Report 1964-65, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:008)
- Southeastern Virginia Tuberculosis and Health Association Annual Report: Your Money Has Opened Doors 1967-68, 1 brochure (Box-folder 420:009)
- Southeastern Virginia Tuberculosis and Health Association Annual Report 1969-70, 1 brochure (Box-folder 420:010)
- Southeastern Virginia Tuberculosis and Health Association Annual Report: Matters of Life and Breath 1972-73, 1 brochure (Box-folder 420:011)
- Southeastern Virginia Tuberculosis and Health Association Annual Report 1973-74, 1 brochure (Box-folder 420:012)
- Virginia Lung Association Annual Report: speech ... laughter ... yells ... sighs ... 1975-76, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:013)
- Virginia Lung Association Annual Report: Lung disease changes everything 1976-77, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:014)
- Virginia Lung Association Annual Report: Every breath you take ... we care 1977-78, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:015)
- Virginia Lung Association Annual Report: Matters of life and breath 1978-79, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:016)
- Virginia Lung Association Annual Report 1979-80, 1 brochure (Box-folder 420:017)
- Virginia Lung Association Annual Report: The "Christmas Seal" people at work 1980-81, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:018)
- American Lung Association of Virginia Annual Report 1981-82, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:019)
- American Lung Association of Virginia Annual Report 1982-83, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 420:020)
- Ann Landers and unidentified man 1963?, 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 420:021)
- Southeastern Virginia Tuberculosis and Health Association building 1965 May 19, 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 420:022)
- G. Conoly Phillips, Jack B. Prince, Debbie Wood and Charles R. Grandy III 1971?, 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 420:023)
- Outdoor photo of double-barred cross and sign to buy and use Christmas seals N.D., 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 420:024)
- Parade float to support Christmas Seals N.D., 2 B&W photos (Box-folder 420:025)
- Girl Scouts help with sale of Christmas Seals N.D., 1 B&W photo (Box-folder 420:026)
- Christmas seal collecting articles written by Betsy and Chuck Berry N.D., 1995-1999, TD, AN (Box-folder 420:027)
- Freedom from Smoking Audiotape Program (Side 1: Stop Smoking Program, Side 2: Relaxation Tape (3 copies) Freedom from Smoking Relaxation Recording (1 copy) c1984, c1991, 4 audiotapes (Box-folder 420:028)
- Just a Reminder Christmas Seals Fight Tuberculosis, Greenbrier-Monroe Tuberculosis & Health Association West Virginia 1950, postcard (Box-folder 420:029)
  donated by Karen Fankhauser, March 26, 2013
- The Southwest virginiia Campaign Against Pollution [Part I]1971January - May, scrapbook (Box-folder 421:000 [oversize])
  With photos, newspaper clippings, letters, and progress reports the 14 1/2" x 20" scrapbook documents the first five months in the campaign to reduce pollution by the Southwest Virginia Tuberculosis and Respiratory Disease Association, the Bristol Herald Courier, and the Bristol Woman's Club. They invited Senior Women's Clubs, the TB-RD Youth Board, the Bristol Chamber of Commerce, Lee Magdez, and the Boy Scouts.
- The Southwest Virginia Campaign Against Pollution [Part 2] 1971 June - December, scrapbook (Box-folder 421:000 [oversize])
  With photos, newspaper clippings, letters, and progress reports the 14 1/2" x 20" scrapbook documents the second seven months in the campaign to reduce pollution.
- Certificate of Recognition: By virtue of the authority vested by the Constitution in the Governor of the Commonwealth of Virginia, there is hereby officially recognized: Christmas Seal Month 2002 December, framed certificate (Box-folder 421:000 [oversize])
  certificate is signed by Mark R. Warner, Governor and Anita A. Rimler, Secretary
- ALAV Scrapbook 2002 December, 19 3/4" x 24 1/2" scrapbook with newspaper clippings (Box-folder 422:000 [oversize])
  The topics of the clippings include smoking (health risks, cessation, smoking bans both pro and con); air quality; radon; SUPERKIDS camp; and fundraising activities such as a golf privilege card, Bike Trek, soccer game, and Christmas seals.
- "A Century of Progress: Virginia's Role in Tuberculosis Control"post 2000, six cloth banners measuring 35" x 24" with wooden dowels (Box-folder 423:000 [oversize])
  The six banners are titled: A Century of Progress, A Century of Tuberculosis Control in Virginia, Christmas Seals and Tuberculosis, Sanatorium Era, Chemotherapy Era, and The Work Continues. The exhibit was funded by a grant from The Tuberculosis Foundation of Virginia, Inc.
- Christmas seals 1923-1998, four notebooks containing Christmas seals and 52 folders (Box-folder 424:000 [oversize])
  The four notebooks contain Christmas seals from (1) 1945-1989; (2) 1943-1991; (3) 1934-1997 and 1998 Valentine test and Easter fund seals; and (4) 1952-1961, 1963, 1965-1972, 1975-1987 and 1989-1991. The folders contain stamps divided by years. The earliest stamp is from 1927; the latest from 2014.
- "Our First Century: American Lung Association 100 Years 1904-2004" post 2004, 24" x 36" poster on foam board (Box-folder unboxed)